



□ +380935374841 | Main hi@shal.dev | Ashal.dev | In ashanaakh

"With hard work and effort, you can achieve anything."

Summary.

Currently Middle Golang Engineer at J:Mind:Systems. More than two years of experience specializing in the backend, concurrency and microservices. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools. As for sport I like swimming and cycling. Travelling is my passion, I like to discover new places and inspire by amazing views.

Skill Highlights

Programming Languages Golang, Ruby, Python, C++

Microservices Docker, Kubernetes Cloud Terraform, AWS, GCP Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, Redis Languages English, Russian, Ukrainian

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

BACHELOR IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

• My GPA is 4.39/5

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

MASTER IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Kyiv, Ukraine

2015 - 2019

Kyiv, Ukraine

2019 - PRESENT

Oct. 2019 - PRESENT

Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

Kyiv, Ukraine

Jun. 2019 - Apr. 2019

Experience

J:Mind:Systems Kyiv, Ukraine

GOLANG ENGINEER

- Designing and implementation of different APIs
- OpenAPI/Swagger specification for APIs
- Automation of KYC verification
- Work with AWS services: S3, Rekognition, Aurora
- Work with Tesseract OCR Engine
- Designing database schema
- Documentation for the software
- Interviewing new candidates

OpenCars Kyiv, Ukraine

GOLANG ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- Telegram bot management
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation

OpenWare Kyiv, Ukraine Dec. 2018 - Oct. 2019

GOLANG ENGINEER

- Writing idiomatic and resillient Go code
- Software architecture construction and designing
- Specifications and requirements development
- Code review
- High loaded software development
- · Closely coached and mentored new project member

MyTimeTable DEVOPS

• Inftastructure as code development

- Implementation of docker images • Implementation of CI/CD pipelines
- Managing project on DigitalOcean

ALI SHANAAKH

Helios Technologies

DEVOPS & BACKEND ENGINEER

Kyiv, Ukraine Jun. 2017 - Dec. 2018

- Ruby on Rails Development
- Golang development
- · Assembling components using Docker
- DevOps tools development
- Managing projects on Google Cloud Platform
- Build plugins for CI/CD tools
- Build advanced deployments using Kubernetes
- Development of complicated terraform modules
- Design & Implement in-cluster high-speed workers

Palestine Nights

CO-FOUNDER & FULL STACK ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation
- Development of APIs
- DigitalOcean deployment automation

Al Muharraq, Bahrain

Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

Program Committees.

2018 Team Member, Google Hash Code Hackathon Kyiv, Ukraine 2018 **Opensource Initiative Winner**, Websummit Lisbon, Portugal 2019 Visitor, iForum Kyiv, Ukraine Visitor, IT Weekends Kyiv, Ukraine 2019

ALI SHANAAKH